https://dermaglow.com/privacy-policy-2/

The Policy is designed
to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal
information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions
when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be
continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our
customers’ needs.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Web
site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you
knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web
site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse
our Web site.
1. Personal Information You Choose to Provide
For example, you may
need to provide the following information:
NameWebsite URL
informationEmail addressHome and business
phone number
In addition to
providing the foregoing information, if you choose to correspond further with
us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together
with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for
these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of
information received by mail and telephone.
2. Web Site Use Information
Similar to other
commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called
“cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and
Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used.
Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date
and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web
sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is
collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with
you as an individual.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide
to Us?
Broadly speaking, we
use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities,
providing customer service and making available other products and services to
our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the
information we collect to notify you about new services and special offers we
think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service
offers are developed and managed and designed to safeguard the security and
privacy of our customers’ personal information. As a customer, you will be
given the opportunity.
What Are Cookies?
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to
recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of
data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies
can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify
subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the
information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This
makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete
commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience
easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from
Cookies?
We use Web site
browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather
information about our Web site users’ browsing activities, in order to
constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This
information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most
user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the
needs of our customers and prospective customers.
Cookies help us
collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the
cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move
from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people
visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site’s visitor capacity. We do not use
these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally
identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused
online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We utilize
encryption/security best practices to safeguard the confidentiality of personal
information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental
loss, alteration or destruction.
Communication Opt Out
If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from Dermaglow you can unsubscribe by following the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you located at the footer of the communication. We can be reached by postal mail at
936-B 7th St, #147, Novato, CA 94947 or by phone at 888-345-4569. You can email us at bjohnk@dermaglow.com with questions, comments or suggestions.
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?
We may provide
aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and
related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but
this information will not include personally identifying data, except as
otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.
What about Legally Compelled Disclosure of
Information?
We may disclose
information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good
faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal
rights.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web
Site?
We are not responsible
for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the
information or content contained therein.
